(Sheldon:)I'll say it looks good.
(Sheldon:)It's in my proprietary
font, Shelvetica.
(Leonard:)I want to say
something obnoxious,
(Leonard:)but it is easy on the eyes.
(Bernadette:)I'm a little tired, Howie.
You ready to go?
(Howard:)Yeah, one sec. I just need
to sign this contract.
(Bernadette:)What is it?
Well, we ran into a problem
(Howard:)about my share of the patent,
so we're forming
(Howard:)a partnership to split
anything we make equally.
(Penny:)Sheldon, did you draft
the contract?
(Sheldon:)You bet I did.
(Penny:)Ooh. You're gonna make
out so hard tonight.
(Bernadette:)So, you're
just gonna sign this
(Bernadette:)without having
a lawyer look at it?
(Sheldon:)Excuse me.
(Sheldon:)I've been drafting contracts
since kindergarten.
(Sheldon:)Didn't need a lawyer to get me
out of finger painting.
(Sheldon:)Don't need one now.
(Penny:)I know, but...
Bernie,
(Howard:)the guys were nice enough
to find a way
(Howard:)to keep me from being cut out.
(Bernadette:)Well, I should hope so.
(Bernadette:)The whole thing was your idea.
(Amy:)Well, to be fair, Howard's idea
was based on Sheldon's math.